[
  {
    "question": "Where did we go on our very first date?",
    "answer": "Shanghai",
    "choices": ["Shanghai", "Suzhou", "Kunshan", ""]
  },
  {
    "question": "On what exact date (DDMMYYYY) did we meet?",
    "answer": "18-08-2023",
    "choices": ["19-08-2023", "17-08-2023", "18-08-2023"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cats or dogs?",
    "answer": "Cats",
    "choices": ["Cats", "Dogs", "Both", "Neither"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Cats or dogs?",
    "answer": "Cats",
    "choices": ["Cats", "Dogs", "Both", "Neither"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What’s my absolute favorite ice-cream flavor?",
    "answer": "Coffee",
    "choices": ["Coffee", "Chocolate", "Vanilla", "Strawberry"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which pizza topping do I always pick off before eating?",
    "answer": "None",
    "choices": ["Olives", "Mushrooms", "Peppers", "None"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the name of my favorite anime?",
    "answer": "One Piece",
    "choices": ["Attack on Titan", "One Piece", "Dragon Ball"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Texting or voice notes?",
    "answer": "Voice notes",
    "choices": ["Texting", "Voice notes", "Both", "Neither"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Favorite Dessert?",
    "answer": "Tiramisu",
    "choices": ["Brownie", "Tiramisu", "Cheese Cake", "Dark Forest Cake"]
  },
  {
    "question": "At what exact minute does my alarm usually go off?",
    "answer": "08:15",
    "choices": ["07:10", "07:30", "08:00", "08:15"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What do I hate the most about you?",
    "answer": "Nothing",
    "choices": ["Your attitude", "Your morning breath", "Nothing"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When it’s movie night, what snack do I always reach for first?",
    "answer": "You",
    "choices": ["Chips", "Popcorn", "Chocolate", "You"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank: “Pancakes are only complete with a dash of _____.”",
    "answer": "Amlou",
    "choices": ["Honey", "Maple syrup", "Amlou"]
  },

  {
    "question": "Which country tops my must-visit list?",
    "answer": "Pakistan",
    "choices": ["Japan", "Senegal", "Egypt", "Pakistan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What musical instrument do I wish I could play?",
    "answer": "Piano",
    "choices": ["Guitar", "Piano", "Drums"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which language am I determined to learn next?",
    "answer": "Spanish",
    "choices": ["French", "Spanish", "German"]
  }
]